KEVIN PAUL

MACHINE LEARNING ENGINEER

: Regency Apts 801 Sardar Patel Rd, Chennai-600113

&: +91 9962222991

OBJECTIVE

Professional and Positive work ethic-oriented Information Technology major currently attending College of Engineering, Guindy (Anna University), with 4 months of work experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of Emerging Data Science Technologies, Application Development, and Image Processing skills to successfully fill the Machine Learning integrated role at your company. Frequently praised as focused and perseverant by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

EDUCATION -

College of Engineering, Guindy

July 2017- Apr 2022

Bachelor of Technology (B. Tech) in
Information Technology

 Chettinad Vidyashram June 2005 - Apr 2017
 Higher Secondary School

KEY SKILLS -

- Leadership
- Technical Ability
- Analytical Thinking
- Work Ethic
- Conflict Resolution

EXPERIENCE

Spritle Software

Machine Learning Intern (Oct 2020- Dec 2020)

Worked in a robust computer enhanced environment where ML dwells deep into technical and mechanical workplaces. Involved in working in real time ComputerVision integrated projects where datasets are collected, analyzed and trained to obtain meaningful algorithms to complement work rate and produce a convenient and idealistic resolution.

• 3G Institute of Research and Policy Studies <u>Technical Intern</u> (Nov 2019 - Dec 2019)

A one-month internship on the various aspects of Computer Vision and Image Processing to be used practically with

several hands-on projects done in an IoT medium using the Blynk Cloud Environment. Learnt several different applications of Neural Networking as well.

TECHNICAL SKILL

Programming Languages:

- C++
- Python
- JavaScript

Fields with Experience in:

- Image Processing
- Data Science
- Deep Learning
- Computer Vision